<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Polygonal Talk</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 11:00:13 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 11:00:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everybody&#39;s Gone to the Rapture : Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve never played a “walking simulator” before this, but I’m glad I did. This is the Bizarro-Destiny of games, where it is ALL story and no gameplay. And it works. REALLY well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll try not to repeat myself from above, but just know that none of that stuff changed. Slightly creepy, immensely lonely, R2 to run… all that is still in the latter half of the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;graphics&quot;&gt;Graphics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This game is gorgeous. From the very first scene where you are looking out over a valley at a sunrise, to the final moments (I won’t spoil that scene) I was thoroughly impressed with what the CryEngine 3 can do. From the time shifts, to the weather changes to the sparks falling from the light balls that zip around the town, I was in awe at everything. And you get to really take it all in due to the slow pace you’ll be walking at. I really should have hitten the “Share” button once or twice, but I was so into everything going on around me that it never popped into my head to do so. I will definitely take advantage of that during my next Trophy hunting playthroughs. My only complaint is the framerate. It really, REALLY struggles at times, especially noticeable in the shadows. I’m hoping they fix this via patch as it was jarring enough to take me out of the moment several times. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2015-vs-everybodys-gone-to-the-rapture&quot;&gt;You can read more about that here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sound&quot;&gt;Sound&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music. Wow. It is subtle at times and others it sent chills down my spine at just the right moment. Certain actions trigger more intense music and when nothing is going on, sometimes the background sound effects fill the atmosphere with a sense of life, yet utter loneliness. I’m talking gibberish. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theguardian.com/technology/2015/jul/30/everybodys-gone-to-the-rapture-video-game-sound-music&quot;&gt;Here is a great article that explains it way better than I can.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gameplay&quot;&gt;Gameplay&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well… hmm… this is an interactive story—with much less emphasis on “interactive” than on “story.” There isn’t much here. You wander around, with the light trails gently nudging you in the correct directions, you press X a few times and tip your controller in one direction or another at certain points. And, yet… it was fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This game DOES NOT hand-hold. If you are looking for a Batman Arkham Knight game that puts a dot on a map with a trail of arrows pointing you in the right direction and constant button prompts, this is not that game. I didn’t even figure out that I could hop certain fences until later in the game. This made me miss out on some story elements. But then again, I don’t think you’re supposed to catch everything the first time. And you get so used to NOT interacting with things, that you miss some Trophy opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.ytimg.com/vi/aU4WT2LqpMA/maxresdefault.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;http://i.guim.co.uk/img/static/sys-images/Guardian/Pix/pictures/2015/6/19/1434715708491/7e7cbf63-e4c4-409d-8d4b-cfd1205319ab-620x372.jpeg?w=620&amp;amp;q=85&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;sharp=10&amp;amp;s=1aebff12c03382ac460344505d6e698e&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;story&quot;&gt;Story&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What can I say? The whole game is story and it’s a good one. You “meet” various characters, and you follow them through the events that led to their disappearance. You get to see their personalities, good or bad, their struggles, their fears at what was going on… and in some cases, these stories nearly made my eyes water. Ok, maybe a little bit. Especially, the one that ends at a [spoiler]train station.[/spoiler] Even though you… hmm… I guess I have to leave that sentence unfinished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ending. Let’s just say that my prediction in a previous post was… partially… correct. I think. See, the ending doesn’t hold your hand either, but hopefully you’ve uncovered enough of the pieces leading up to it to grasp the meaning. I actually can’t wait until more of you have played through it so we can discuss our interpretations of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/FQw0Fhl.gif&quot; alt=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/FQw0Fhl.gif&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nitpicksmisc&quot;&gt;Nitpicks/Misc&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Trophies. By the way, DO NOT read them before playing through the first time. One is kinda spoilery… kind of. But mostly, you’ll be focused on finding these things than what’s going on around you and you’ll miss the immersion which is why I think most of these trophies are things that won’t pop during a normal playthrough. They’d be distracting. Most of them require you to find something or somewhere and… do nothing. For minutes at a time. Others are finding everything of a certain type… very challenging. And then the final 2, well… that Platinum will be worth it. After I completed the game last night, I instantly began a new one because I missed an entire area early on. I got some more story there, one key piece I wish I had found the first time, and started the trophy hunt. I’ll need to play the entire story at least twice more to get them all. Whatever. It’s a great game that didn’t take a lot of time to complete—I’ll gladly play this game again and again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, the only downsides are the framerate, the slow pace (which you can speed up slightly if you have to backtrack) and the fan… oh, yeah… the PS4 fan. I’ve read that the menu screens in this game do not have a capped framerate. So if you spend enough time looking at one, the framerate will skyrocket and your PS4’s fan will kick in and it will not stop until you quit the game. I had it running in the background and went to Netflix and the fan was out-of-control until I went back to the game and force quit it. That can be patched. Hopefully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, I highly recommend this game as a nice change of pace to Destiny, Rocket League or some other action-packed title. If you want a quality story, with a beautiful environment, engaging dialogue, nifty music and have a few hours—this is the game. I recommend playing with headphones to get all the ambience and locking away family members, so you have no distractions. Also, finish it in 2 or 3 sessions, max, close together so you don’t forget character’s names or voices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9 out of 10&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I’d love, love, love to see this as a Morpheus title one day.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 23:34:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/review/2015/10/10/everyones-gone-to-the-rapture-review.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/review/2015/10/10/everyones-gone-to-the-rapture-review.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>review</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quote Test</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Dang. Not a single piece of bad news here. I’m actually excited to play this now having watched that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/quotes/2015/10/10/quote-test.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/quotes/2015/10/10/quote-test.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>quotes</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quote Test</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve learned to disassociate “Playable Drake” from “Cutscene/Story Drake”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/quotes/2015/10/09/quote-test.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/quotes/2015/10/09/quote-test.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>quotes</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quote Test</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I scored via Bicycle Keek! and forgot to save it. So pissed off.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/quotes/2015/10/08/quote-test.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/quotes/2015/10/08/quote-test.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>quotes</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Material Design Lite</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;But it’s not who you are underneath… it’s what you do that defines you. Death does not wait for you to be ready! Death is not considerate of fair! And make no mistake, here you face death. Tiger. Jujitsu. Panther. You’re skilled. But this is not a dance. And you are afraid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theatricality and deception, powerful agents to the uninitiated. But we are initiated aren’t we, Bruce? Members of the League of Shadows. And you betrayed us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It means you’re hatred, and it also means losing someone, who I’ve cared for since I first heard his cries echoing through this house. But it might also mean saving your life. And that is more important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I seek the means to fight injustice. To turn fear against those who prey on the fearful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know how to fight six men. We can teach you how to engage 600.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you see… I’m buying this hotel and setting some new rules about the pool area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty soon we will be chasing down over due library books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or perhaps he’s wondering why someone would shoot a man before throwing him out of the plane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Merely Ducard but I speak for Ra’s al Ghul… a man greatly feared by the criminal underworld. A mon who can offer you a path. Someone like you is only here by choice. You have been exploring the criminal fraternity but whatever your original intentions you have to become truly lost. The path of a man who shares his hatred of evil and wishes to serve true justice. The path of the League of Shadows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay. Now… Hardened Kevlar plates over titanium-dipped, tri-weave fibers for flexibility. You’ll be lighter, faster, more agile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re good at something, never do it for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not just your name, sir. It’s your father’s name. And it’s all that’s left of him. Don’t destroy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Punishment Must Be More Severe.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 08:34:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/review/2015/09/11/material-design-lite.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/review/2015/09/11/material-design-lite.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>review</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Link Test</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I scored via Bicycle Keek! and forgot to save it. So pissed off.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/quotes/2015/09/08/link-test.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/quotes/2015/09/08/link-test.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>quotes</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jekyll Material Design Lite</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet esse et laborum, ground round hamburger venison rump meatball frankfurter cow capicola ut. Boudin dolore capicola, consequat ut filet mignon dolor duis incididunt. Frankfurter esse qui venison. Chuck adipisicing cillum excepteur laborum ex filet mignon landjaeger quis dolore kevin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jerky consequat quis tri-tip pork prosciutto short ribs est ham hock consectetur. Dolore mollit fatback kevin, pork belly pastrami officia excepteur venison laborum strip steak in doner. Aliqua sausage spare ribs meatloaf meatball.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rump t-bone ad tenderloin tempor shank aliquip, frankfurter cupidatat landjaeger id tongue prosciutto kevin. Irure laborum brisket, doner exercitation ipsum anim sirloin magna tail jowl fugiat meatloaf alcatra. Jowl sed meatball spare ribs pork et ullamco duis. Incididunt deserunt porchetta sirloin ground round, leberkas aliquip corned beef anim biltong ea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consectetur chicken salami lorem. Pancetta mollit aliqua sirloin ut officia short ribs ribeye ham hock occaecat shoulder incididunt. Laborum duis sausage id. Beef landjaeger sed leberkas tail doner spare ribs cupidatat fatback sausage. Filet mignon spare ribs quis shoulder pancetta ut eiusmod dolore. Venison velit in, landjaeger irure consectetur minim ham deserunt shoulder. Veniam corned beef t-bone sint consequat.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 04:34:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2015/08/11/jekyll-mdl.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2015/08/11/jekyll-mdl.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;Tom&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &amp;#39;Hi, Tom&amp;#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll-help&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s dedicated Help repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 06:34:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/2015/07/11/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/2015/07/11/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
